<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>takara.ai</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content on takara.ai</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:11:53 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Carlos Miguens</title><link>http://localhost:1313/company/team/2024-07-01-carlos-miguens/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/company/team/2024-07-01-carlos-miguens/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Marty Legg</title><link>http://localhost:1313/company/team/2024-07-01-marty-legg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/company/team/2024-07-01-marty-legg/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Jordan Legg</title><link>http://localhost:1313/company/team/jordan-legg/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:30:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/company/team/jordan-legg/</guid><description>Hello World</description></item><item><title>Mega Prompts</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/mega-prompts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 12:25:23 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/mega-prompts/</guid><description>Contributors:
Bailey Readings CEO of GrantScout.AI | Founder of AutomatedFlow.Ai Jordan Legg Chief AI Officer What Are MegaPrompts? MegaPrompts are enhanced, detailed instructions given to a LLM to guide their responses and actions. Unlike standard prompts, which are often brief and lack context, MegaPrompts provide comprehensive information to achieve more accurate, efficient, and high-quality outputs.
Key Components of a MegaPrompt MegaPrompts may contain the following ASPECCTs:
Action:
A clear statement of the task or action the LLM needs to perform.</description></item><item><title>Product Prototypes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/product-prototypes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:15:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/product-prototypes/</guid><description>Instruction Following Prompt Guide:
&amp;#34;Create a product prototype for [PRODUCT_DESCRIPTION] by following these steps: 1. Define the problem the product aims to solve and identify the target users, considering [TARGET_USER_CHARACTERISTICS]. 2. Sketch out the basic design and features of the product, focusing on [KEY_FEATURES]. 3. Create a low-fidelity prototype using [PROTOTYPING_TOOL], incorporating [DESIGN_ELEMENTS]. 4. Develop a high-fidelity prototype with interactive elements and a polished design using [PROTOTYPING_PLATFORM]. 5. Test the prototype with [NUMBER_OF_USERS] potential users and gather feedback on [FEEDBACK_AREAS] for improvements.</description></item><item><title>Startups</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/startups/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 20:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/startups/</guid><description>Founders Agreements Zero-Shot Prompt Guide:
&amp;#34;Outline the key components of a founders agreement for a startup, focusing on equity distribution, roles and responsibilities, decision-making processes, and dispute resolution. Ensure the guide is comprehensive and adaptable for different startup needs without relying on specific examples.&amp;#34; Instruction Following Prompt Guide:
&amp;#34;Create a founders agreement template for a startup by following these instructions: 1. Define the equity distribution among founders and conditions for changes.</description></item><item><title>Prompt Guide</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/prompt-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/prompt-guide/</guid><description>Welcome to the world of prompt engineering! This guide is designed to help you navigate the exciting landscape of AI communication with confidence and creativity. By understanding the different learning methods, utilizing placeholders effectively, and following the prompt guide format, you&amp;rsquo;ll be well-equipped to unlock the full potential of our tutorials and achieve your goals more efficiently. These guides were handcrafted by our team here at takara.ai (although the structure of these is assisted by AI) completely for free in our spare time and we hope you enjoy them.</description></item><item><title>Marketing</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/marketing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/prompt-engineering/marketing/</guid><description>Proposal Pitch Decks Instruction Following Prompt Guide:
Create a pitch deck for [YOUR_PRODUCT_OR_SERVICE] targeting [TYPE_OF_AUDIENCE] by following these steps: 1. Begin with an engaging introduction that highlights the main problem [YOUR_PRODUCT_OR_SERVICE] solves. 2. Briefly describe your product or service and its unique value proposition. 3. Identify your target market and explain why your solution is the best fit for them. 4. Provide an overview of your business model and how you plan to generate revenue.</description></item><item><title>GPT Models</title><link>http://localhost:1313/open-source/custom-gpts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/open-source/custom-gpts/</guid><description>At takara.ai, we&amp;rsquo;ve crafted a suite of custom GPT models tailored for specific applications that are reshaping industries. Discover our lineup of AI solutions and elevate your operational capabilities.
COMMIT HELPER | コミットヘルパー Simplify Your Development Workflow
Quickly generate standardized commit messages to maintain a clean git history. Ideal for streamlining your DevOps practices.
Effortless Integration: Seamlessly blends into your existing workflow. Standardization: Adheres to conventional commit specifications. Productivity Boost: Save time for what matters in development.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>http://localhost:1313/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Welcome to Takara.ai (&amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), an AI consultancy dedicated to showcasing our services through our website. Your privacy is critically important to us, and this Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we collect and record, how it&amp;rsquo;s used, and how we safeguard your data.
1. Information Collection and Use Personal Data We collect personal data through our contact form, such as your name and email address. This data is necessary for us to communicate with you, respond to your inquiries, and facilitate the provision of our services should you wish to engage with us.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>http://localhost:1313/company/about-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 20:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/company/about-us/</guid><description>Takara means treasure. Welcome to takara.ai, where we harness artificial intelligence as a transformative force for businesses and humanity. Founded in 2024, our consultancy is committed to unlocking AI&amp;rsquo;s vast potential, empowering individuals and organisations to excel in an increasingly competitive landscape.
The Challenge: Mastering AI Implementation At takara.ai, we address a critical market gap: the disparity between AI&amp;rsquo;s promise and its practical implementation. Businesses often struggle with:
Selecting the right models.</description></item><item><title>Ethics</title><link>http://localhost:1313/company/ethics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 12:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/company/ethics/</guid><description>At takara.ai, we are committed to developing AI with integrity. We believe that ethical AI is the cornerstone of trust and innovation. Our technology is designed with the highest ethical standards, ensuring fairness, transparency, and accountability at every step. We strive to empower society with AI that enhances human capabilities while respecting privacy and promoting inclusivity.
How Do We Do This? Explainable AI (XAI): Develop AI systems that are explainable and understandable to users, providing clear insights into how and why decisions are made.</description></item></channel></rss>